all right here we go I'm going to make a
video potatoes you're like why is this
guy making a video of potatoes I'm
telling you if you want to live out of
your car or you're going to live on your
bike uh one of the best things you can
get is these these potatoes um I happen
to like The Buttery ones here's
something that you might not think about
that took me over a year to discover you
don't need a dish for this no all right
so so just to show you you get um what
is this you get like
uh there's 110 calories per
serving but there are four servings per
per thing and four serving I mean if you
if you're okay with eating four servings
which is a lot that's like what is that
four times 110 4400 4 440 calories I
mean that's pretty much a meal right but
if you're if you're a big time biker or
you you you're burning a lot of calories
and you you want to eat some stuff and
you want it to be pretty cheap um again
I'm there's no affiliate link for this I
just want to tell you just this
discovery the discovery I made is that
all you really need to do I have a I
have a a kettle heater I don't even use
a gas stove anymore if I was on my bike
I would but I have an electric powered
um pot it's a kettle and it it heats up
the water to the point where it needs to
be in like under a minute and then you
just pour the water straight into the
thing I know that's the thing that I
never thought of you pour the water in
there and make sure you're you know it's
kind of hot so you kind of be careful
and then mix it up slowly in there and
pour some more water and mix it up
slowly guess what you just saved
yourself a dish and if you're living out
of your car you know what I'm talking
about you know you know that you do not
want those extra dishes and by the way
potatoes potatoes are like the worst
possible thing to get on a dish they are
the hardest thing to clean off instant
potatoes are one of the worst things to
clean off a dish so you're
welcome by the way if you buy them in
bulk like I have here on the screen um
somebody was telling me you can get the
price of you can get the price of mass
potatoes per serving so that thing down
down to under a buck so if you're
looking for carbs and you are burning a
lot of carbs like I am uh and you want
something by the way that's very low fod
map and I don't know if you know what
that means
um I there's other carbs that I can't do
so any kind of weeds or something like
that I I blow out like a balloon when I
try to eat it um that's just me I know
it's an old man thing but but I can eat
potatoes potatoes are really solidly
potatoes and corn chips anything corn
related does not mess me up so so I
found i' this has been one of the best
best things it's actually really
satisfying it's a nice warm meal when
it's cold out side I remember when I was
um testing a bunch of of cold weather
Rigs and and Tents and thing that just
being able to make um you know a hot
thing to hold in your hands a hot thing
of potatoes is like really really
satisfying I I know that seems like
Overkill but there's some of you out
there that going to appreciate this and
you're going to know exactly what I'm
talking about so every once in a while
you want a hot meal and those cold meals
are not doing it and when that's times
come just eat up some water and dump
them in your potatoes you're done so
that's that that's all there for that